eletsonline.com 2016-12-31

# Privacy Policy | Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd.

Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd. takes the privacy of its users seriously. Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd. has adopted information management guidelines for our customer relationships designed to respect the privacy and preferences of our users.

Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd. receives your information through our website, applications ads, and commerce services. This Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd. Privacy Policy describes how and when Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd. collects, uses, and shares your information when you use our services and website.

**What Type of Information does Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd. collect?**  
Personal information collected by Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd. may include:

* Name, postal address, phone number, and e-mail address.
* Financial account information, such as credit card number and other payment information. Please note, we do not retain credit card information.

We may also collect information about you such as:

* If you create an account – your username, password, and other demographic information that you provide.
* If you purchase from Elets Technomedia – what you buy, and how frequently you buy.
* If you take a survey or interact with us in various other ways – demographics information that you provide and information about subjects that may interest you.
* If you connect your account to another service such as Facebook, LinkedIn or Twitter, the other service may send us your registration or profile information on that service that you authorize. This information enables cross-platform data sharing to improve your user experience.

We may automatically collect website use information when you visit our site. This information may include information about your Internet service provider, your operating system, browser type, domain name, Internet protocol (IP) address, your access times, the website that referred you to us, the Web pages you request, and the date and time of those requests. Our collection of website use information may involve the use of cookies and web beacons. Cookies are small data files stored on your hard drive by a website to, among other things, help us improve our site and your experience. In addition, this site uses targeting or advertising cookies to see which areas and features are popular and to count visits to our site. These cookies are used by third parties such as social networks and advertisers to collect information about your browsing habits and share it with other websites so they can display advertising relevant to you, provide services, and to allow “Like” buttons and “Share” buttons to work. Most browsers allow you to decline cookies (check your browser’s Help menu) but doing so may disable some features on our site, and prevent us from recognizing you when you return to our site.

Web beacons are electronic images that may be used on our site or in our emails. We use web beacons to deliver cookies, count visits, understand usage and campaign effectiveness, and to tell if an email has been opened and acted upon. We may also use Local Shared Objects (Flash cookies). To identify Local Shared Objects on your computer and adjust your settings, visit: www.macromedia.com/support/documentation/en/flashplayer/help/settings_manager.html.

Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd. may also collect aggregated or anonymized usage data that does not personally identify you.

**How Does Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd. Use Information About You?**  
Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd. may use the information we gather to allow us to process orders, registrations, and customer service inquiries.  
Communicate with you about your orders, purchases, accounts, and requests for information.  
Provide you with information about products and services we offer (if you agree to receive such information).

**Does Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd. Share Personal Information With Third Parties?**  
We do not disclose your personal information except in the limited circumstances described here. We sometimes work with advertisers or other third parties to serve ads targeted to your interests, or to collect data for conversion tracking (that is, what actions you take after you click on an ad).

We retain the email addresses of those who send us email, who purchase goods and services via our website, who register for access to our site, and who subscribe to our email newsletters or the print or digital editions of Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd.. We do not disclose these email addresses to third parties. We do on occasion provide magazine subscribers’ postal mailing addresses to selected advertisers who wish to reach you by mail.

We do use aggregated information (that is, data about our customers or users that is anonymized so that no one is individually identified), to allow us to audit site usage, create marketing profiles, manage our relationship with advertisers, and to provide support services to us.  
How is Personal Information Secured?

Elets Technomedia Pvt. Ltd. maintains appropriate physical, technical and administrative security to help prevent the loss, misuse, unauthorized access, disclosure or modification of personal information.

While we take these steps to protect your personal information as much as we reasonably can, no system or transmission of data over the Internet or any other public network, or any storage of data, can be guaranteed to be 100% secure.
